everyclickmatters.com 2013-12-15

# Privacy | Symantec

_Last Updated: June 10, 2013_

##  As a world leader in Internet security technology, Symantec understands your desire to have your personal information protected. 

**Symantec respects your concerns about privacy and values its relationship with you.** This Notice describes the types of information we collect via Symantec’s web sites as set out below, how we may use that information and with whom we may share it. Our Privacy Notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the information. We also tell you how you may contact us to update your information, remove your name from our mailing lists or get answers to questions you may have about our privacy practices at Symantec. 

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.symantec.com&sealid=101) Symantec is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent initiative whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the principles of disclosure and informed consent. TRUSTe certifies the following sites: www.symantec.com in North America; TRUSTe’s certification does not cover the Symantec Store (shop.symantecstore.com – see Privacy Policy for details). Because our sites want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

### Privacy Facts Statement

The Privacy Facts Statement provides a short summary of our privacy practices. Learn more about the Privacy Facts Statement.

### Norton Anti-Theft Privacy Policy

The Norton Anti-theft Privacy Policy details what information is collected through Norton Anti-Theft, and how Symantec uses that information. Learn more about [Norton Anti-Theft Privacy Policy](https://antitheft.norton.com/privacy).

### Norton Community Watch Privacy Policy

Norton Community Watch is a voluntary program for our customers to participate in sharing information concerning threats on the Internet, which allows Symantec to evaluate and update our protection for the benefit of all customers. This policy describes what information is collected and how it is used. Learn more about the Norton Community Watch Privacy Policy.

### Norton AntiSpam Privacy Policy

The Norton AntiSpam Privacy Policy details what information is collected through Norton AntiSpam, and how Symantec uses information submitted by reported spam. Learn more about Norton AntiSpam Privacy Policy.

### Norton Online Family Privacy Policy

Norton Online Family is a service for parents to help in monitoring and protecting their children’s online experiences. This policy describes how information is collected and used in Norton Online Family. Learn more about [Norton Online Family Privacy Policy](https://onlinefamily.norton.com/familysafety/privacypolicy.jsp).

### Social Media Privacy Policy

Our Social Media Privacy Policy governs sites which include user-generated content and social, business or technical networking, and addresses the issues arising from sharing information in those contexts. Learn more about the Social Media Privacy Policy.

### LiveUpdate Privacy Notice

LiveUpdate is a part of many Symantec products that provides for active updating of products in order to ensure up-to-date protection. This policy describes the information collected and how it is used. Learn more about the LiveUpdate Privacy Notice.
